Contact

karen.cope@stelizabeth.com

www.linkedin.com/in/karenrasso-rn-msn-cmsrn-021b51120 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Registered Nurses Nursing Nursing Management

Karen Rasso RN, MSN, CMSRN

Assistant Nurse Manager Spine & Orthopedic Unit at St Elizabeth Hospital

Hebron, Kentucky

Summary

Experienced Assistant Nurse Manager with demonstrated leadership working at a fast paced inpatient acute care hospital. Skilled in Nursing Management, Acute Care, Nursing, Management, Spine and Orthopedics. Strong operations professional with a Master's degree focused in Nursing Administration from University of Cincinnati.

Experience

St. Elizabeth Healthcare 10 years 11 months

Assistant Nurse Manager-Spine & Orthopedic Unit March 2016 - Present (4 years 4 months) Florence, KY

Staff Registered Nurse (4SE & Spine & Orthopedic Unit) July 2010 - March 2016 (5 years 9 months)

Florence, Kentucky

Nursing Assistant- 4SE August 2009 - July 2010 (1 year) Florence, Kentucky

Education

University of Cincinnati

Master's degree, Nursing Administration · (2014 - 2016)

Northern Kentucky University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2005 - 2010)